A Guide to the John Z. Bowers papers FA1415
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission History, 1.9 Cubic Feet
  - Reprints (Box 34, Folder 548)
    "Research Plan for RERF STudies of the Potential Genetic Effects of Atomic Radiation: Hiroshima and Nagasaki"; "Medical X-Ray Exposure Among Hiroshima and Nagasaki A-Bomb Survivors" by Walter J. Russell; "Studies of the Mortality of A-Bomb Survivors. 1. Plan of Study and Mortality in the Medical Subsample (Selection I), 1950-1958" by Gilbert W. Beebe, Morihiro Ishida, and Seymour Jablon; "Current Status of ABCC-NIH Studies of Carcinogenesis in Hiroshima and Nagasaki" by L.J. Zeldis, S. Jablon, and M. Ishida; "Reflections on the Work of the Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission in Japan" by Gilbert W. Beebe; "On the Significance of Cause of Death as Recorded on Death Certificates in Hiroshima and Nagasaki, Japan" by S. Jablon, D.M. Angevine, Y.S. Matsumoto, and M. Ishida; "Incidence of Leukemia in Atomic Bomb Survivors Belonging to a Fixed Cohort in Hiroshima and Nagasaki, 1950-71: Radiation Dose, Years After Exposure, Age at Exposure, and Type of Leukemia" by Michito Ichimaru, Toranosuke Ishimaru, and Joseph L. Belsky; "Cytogenetic Studies in Exposed Survivors, Hiroshima and Nagasaki" by Arthur D. Bloom, Shotaro Neriishi, Nanao Kamada, Tetsuya Iseki, and Robert J. Keehn; "Genetic Heterogeneity in Human Acatalasia" by Howard B. Hamilton and James V. Neel
  - Radiation Data (Box 34, Folder 549)
    "Ionizing Radiation and Health" by Gilbert W. Beebe; "Studies of Mortality of A-Bomb Survivors. 6. Mortality and Radiation Dose, 1950-1974" by Gilbert W. Beebe, Hiroo Kato, and Charles E. Land; Clippings
  - Keith Cannan (Box 34, Folder 550)
    "The Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission, The First Fourteen Years" by R. Keith Cannan; Biographical Information; Memoir
  - James V. Neel (Box 34, Folder 551)
    "The Effects of Parental Consanguinity and Inbreeding in Hirado, Japan. III. Vision and Hearing" by J.V. Neel, W.J. Shcull, T. Kimura, Y. Tanigawa, M. Yamamoto, and A. Nakajima; "The Effects of Parental Consanguinity and Inbreeding in Hirado, Japan. II. Physical Development, Tapping Rate, Blood Pressure, Intelligence Quotient, and School Performance" by James V. Neel, William J. Schull, Manabu Yamamoto, Satoshi Uchida, Toshiyuki Yanase, and Norio Fujiki; Notes and Curriculum Vitae
  - In Utero (Box 34, Folder 552)
    "Outcome of Pregnancy in Women Exposed to the Atomic Bomb in Nagasaki" by James N. Yamazaki, Stanley W. Wright, and Phyllis M. Wright; "A Study of the Outcome of Pregnancy in Women Exposed to the Atomic Bomb Blast in Nagasaki" by James N. Yamazaki, Stanley W. Wright, and Phyllis M. Wright
  - Radiation Effects Research Foundation (Box 34, Folder 553)
  - Hiroshima, 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 554)
    Notes, Brochures, Correspondence, Translations; "Cops and Robbers" by Goro Shitanda
  - ABCC History, To Do, Notes (Box 34, Folder 555)
  - Unfoldered Materials (Box 35, Folder 556)
    Notebook, Major Studies, Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission; Notebook, Research Japan
  - "The Chrysanthemum and the Feather Merchant" by Austin Moore Brues (Box 35, Folder 557)
  - Unfoldered Materials (Box 35, Folder 558)
    "Yale and the Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission" by John Z. Bowers; Correspondence, Notes; "Late Effects of Atomic Bomb: Notes on a Study of Former ABCC" by Yoshimasa Matsuzaka
  - Unfoldered Materials (Box 35, Folder 559)
    Notebook, ABCC Notes; Booklet, Token of Esteem to George B. Darling, Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission; "Report of the Committee for Scientific Review of ABCC," February 1975
  - Unfoldered Materials (Box 35, Folder 560)
    "Incidence of Leukemia Among Atomic Bomb Survivors in Relation to Neutron and Gamma Dose, Hiroshima and Nagasaki, 1950-71" by Toranosuke Ishimaru, Masanori Otake, and Michito Ichimaru; "Incidence of Leukemia in Atomic Bomb Survivors, Hiroshima and Nagasaki, 1950-71 by Radiation Dose, Years After Exposure, Age, and Type of Leukemia" by Michito Ichimari, Toaranosuke Ishimaru, Joseph L. Belsky, Takanori Tomiyasu, Naoki Sadamori, Takashi Hoshino, Masao Tomonaga, Nobuhiro Shimizu, and Hiromu Okada; "Radiation Effects Research Foundation, 1975-1978"; "Radiation Effects Research Foundation, Annual Report, 1978-1979"; "Radiation Effects Research Foundation, Annual Report, 1979-1980"
  - Miscellaneous China Material (Box 36, Folder 561)
    "A Doctor's Letters from China Fifty Years Ago" by Vivia B. Appleton; "Lucy Aldrich - Kidnap Letters"; "Chinese University of Hong Kong" (includes photographs); "The Role of U.S. Philanthropic Foundations in International Graduate Medical Education" by John Z. Bowers; "Education of the Physician: International Dimensions Program"
- 1994 Accession, 9.34 Cubic Feet
  This series contains research and reference materials related to several of Bowers' writing projects, including the Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission History, Medicine in Japan, and others. Files include reprints, articles, notes, translations, and materials gifted by Dr. Shields Warren. The series also contains publications produced under the auspices of the Josiah Macy, Jr. Foundation during Bowers' tenure as president. Finally, there is a small subset of personal materials (photographs, a memorial album compiled by Akiko Bowers, etc.).
  - Book Review, "Medical Education in Japan" (Box 36, Folder 562)
  - "Western Medical Pioneers in Feudal Japan," Book Reviews, Correspondence, Manuscripts (Box 36, Folder 563)
  - "Western Medicine in a Chinese Palace," Typed Manuscripts, Book Reviews, Correspondence (Box 36, Folder 564)
  - "When the Twain Meet," Book Reviews, Correspondence, Manuscripts (Box 36, Folder 565)
  - Contents of Collected Papers-Journal Articles, Dr. John Z. Bowers, 1964-1980 (Box 36, Folder 566)
  - Contents of Collected Papers-Journal Articles, Dr. John Z. Bowers, 1964-1980 (Box 37, Folder 567)
  - Radiation Effects Research Foundation / Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission (Box 37, Folder 568)
    "Radiation Effects Research Foundation: Its Origin and Growth" by John Z. Bowers; Notecards; "The Relationship of Gamma and Neutron Radiation to Posterior Lenticular Opacities among Atomic Bomb Survivors in Hiroshima and Nagasaki" by Masanori Otake and William J. Schull; "Studies of the Mortality of A-Bomb Survivors. Report 7. Mortality, 1950-1978: Part II. Mortality from Causes Other than Cancer and Mortality in Early Entrants" by Hiroo Kato, Charles C. Brown, David G. Joel, and William J. Schull; "Breast Cancer among Atomic Bomb Survivors: Relationship of Prognosis to Pathologic Findings" by Masayoshi Tokunaga; "Malignant Breast Tumors among Atomic Bomb Survivors Hiroshima and Nagasaki, 1950-74," by Masayoshi Tokunaga, James E. Norman, Masahide Asano, Shoji Tokuoka, Haruo Ezaki, Issei Nishimori, and Yasukuni Tsuji; "Patterns in Cancer Mortality in the United States and Japan" by Masanori Otake; "The Nonlinear Relationship of Radiation Dose to Chromosome Aberrations among Atomic Bomb Survivors, Hiroshima and Nagasaki" by Masanori Otake; "The Delayed Effects of Radiation Exposure among Atomic Bomb Survivors, Hiroshima and Nagasaki, 1945-79: A Brief Summary" by Stuart C. Finch and Iwao M. Moriyama; "Studies of the Mortality of A-Bomb Survivors. 7. Mortality, 1950-1978: Part I. Cancer Mortality" by Hiroo Kato and William J. Schull; "P. Pedro Arrupe, S.J. and the Atomic Bomb, Hiroshima, with a Summary of His Life, 1907-1981" also "P. Siemes, S.J. Narrative of the Bomb" by John Z. Bowers and Akiko K. Bowers; "Nagasaki Historical Sketches" by Jane Rust and Richard K. Blaisdell
  - Radiation Effects Research Foundation / Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission (Box 37, Folder 569)
    "Nagasaki Historical Sketches" by Jane Rust and Richard K. Blaisdell; "Atomic Bombs, Hiroshima and Nagasaki, August 1945"; "The Story of the Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission"; "Relocation of Hiroshima RERF Suddently Reignited"; "Studies of the Mortality of A-Bomb Survivors, Report 7. Part III. Incidence of Cancer in 1959-1978, Based on the Tumor Registry, Nagasaki" by Toshiro Wakabayashi, Hiroo Kato, Takayoshi Ikeda, and William J. Schull; "An Evaluation of Certain Factors which Influence the 'in Vitro' Migration of Subpopulations of Human Lymphocytes" by John A. Pinkson and Stuart C. Finch; "Leukocyte Counts and Coronary Heart Disease in a Japanese Cohort" by Ross L. Prentice, Ted P. Szatrowski, Toshio Fujikura, HIroo Kato, Mark W. Mason, and Howard B. Hamilton; "Biochemical Genetics Study - One Dimensional Electrophoresis and Enzyme Activity Measurements"; Notes; "Recommendations for Cancer Detection at RERF"; "Multiple Myeloma among Atomic Bomb Survivors in Hiroshima and Nagasaki, 1950-76: Relationship to Radiation Dose Absorbed by Marrow" by Michito Ichimaru, Toranosuke Ishimaru, Motoko Mikami, and Masako Matsunaga; "Yale and the Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission" by John Z. Bowers; "Late Effects among Hiroshima and Nagasaki Survivors" by Shields Warren; "RERF Adults Health Study, Report 6, Results of the Six Examination Cycles, 1968-1980, Hiroshima and Nagasaki"
  - "The New Yorker", 1946; 1985; 1995 (Box 37, Folder 570)
  - Research Articles and Reprints by JZB, 1948-1985 (Box 37, Folder 571)
  - Correspondence and Clippings (Box 38, Folder 572)
  - "Great Medical Schools," Alpha Omega Alpha Installation Banquet Speech (Box 38, Folder 573)
  - National Advisory Committee on the Selection of Physicians, Dentists, and Allied Specialists, Correspondence, 1958; 1961 (Box 38, Folder 574)
  - US Navy Citation, The Legion of Merit and the Purple Heart, 1943 (Box 38, Folder 575)
  - The Legion of Honor, Rank of Chevalier, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 576)
  - The Order of the Rising Sun, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 577)
  - "The Health of Mankind," Handwritten and Typed Manuscripts (Box 38, Folder 578)
  - Shields Warren, Remembrance (Box 38, Folder 579)
    Program, A Memorial Service for Dr. Shields Warren; "Shields Warren: A Remembrance" by John Z. Bowers; "Shields Warren - A Tribute" by John Z. Bowers; Correspondence, Notes
  - Gifts from Shields Warren (Box 38, Folder 580)
    Notebook, "Log of Crossroads," Capt. Shields Warren (MC) USNR, USS Burleson APA 67, May-August 1946; Daily Calendar Notebook, Capt. Shields Warren, MCS USNR, Staff, Com Nav FE, April-June 1947; Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission Photographs; Journal, Comdr. S. Warren, MC, USNR, September-December 1947(?)
  - Envelope (Box 38, Folder 581)
    Roche "Medical Image," 1965, 1972; "Chemtech," 1974; "The Josiah Macy, Jr. Foundation," 1982; "The Bulletin," University of Maryland, 1993, 1994, 1998
  - Envelope (Box 39, Folder 582)
    "Medical Education in Japan, 1969-1988" (The 20th Anniversary of the Japanese Society of Medical Education, 1989); "Medical Education in Japan," 1994; "The Pharos," 1994; "Gettysburg," 1994; Rockefeller Archive Center Newsletter, 1995; "Who's Who" Bowers Entry; Davidge Hall Brochure
  - Unfinished Projects (Box 39, Folder 583)
    China, 1980; Japan Today; The Cambridge History and Geography of Human Disease Project; NIH, Department of Health and Human Services
  - Bibliography Notecards (Box 39, Folder 584)
  - In Memoriam (Box 39, Folder 585)
  - Fujikawa, "Geschicte der Medizin in Japan" Chronology, Notes (Box 40, Folder 586)
  - Baelz-Schottlander (Box 40, Folder 587)
    "Erwin von Vaelz, 1849-1913" by Felix Schottlaender
  - Mohnike Original MS (Box 40, Folder 588)
    "Aanteekeningen over de Geneeskunde der Japanezen" by Otto Mohnike
  - Japanbriefe I (Box 40, Folder 589)
  - Japanbriefe II (Box 40, Folder 590)
  - Female Emperors - Japan - Clipping (Box 40, Folder 591)
  - "Salem and Nagasaki: Their Encounter, 1797-1807" by Madoka Kanai (Box 40, Folder 592)
  - Notes on Japan (Box 40, Folder 593)
  - Illustrations, Schultze (Box 40, Folder 594)
  - "An Outline of Chinese Acupuncture," Nanking College of Traditional Chinese Medicine (Box 40, Folder 595)
  - Ten Rhijne, "Dissertatio de Arthritide, etc." (Box 41, Folder 596)
  - "Erwin Baelz, Medical Pioneer in Japan, A Biographical Sketch" by Gerhard Vescovi (Box 41, Folder 597)
  - "Notes on the Medical Science of the Japanese" by Otto Mohnike (Box 41, Folder 598)
  - Japanbriefe (Box 41, Folder 599)
  - "Life and Works of a German Doctor in Japan - Erwin von Baelz" by Felix Schottlander (Box 41, Folder 600)
  - "Population and Pestilence in T'ang China" by Denis Twitchett, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 601)
  - Photograph, "Copy of Antique Chinese Diagnostic Doll" (Box 42, Folder 602)
  - Choa - H.K. Chinese (Box 42, Folder 603)
    "Transactions of the China Medico-Chirurgical Society, 1845-6" by H.A. Rydings; "Some Ideas Concerning Food and Diet among Hong Kong Chinese: The Constitution and Food Therapy" by Gerald Choa; "Chinese Traditional Medicine and Contemporary Hong Kong" by Gerald Choa
  - "The Story of Chinese Acupuncture and Moxibustion" by Fu Wei-kang and "Medical Education in China" by Huang Chia-ssu (Box 42, Folder 604)
  - Siebold Letters, University of California Library (Box 42, Folder 605)
  - Whitney, Notes on the History of Medical Progress in Japan (Box 42, Folder 606)
  - Koga, Jijiro, "Seiyo i-jutsu denraishi" (Box 42, Folder 607)
  - Ishihara Akira, "Ishi gaku gaisetsu" (Box 43, Folder 608)
  - Photograph of John Z. Bowers (Box 44, Folder 609)
  - "Bulletin," University of Maryland, Baltimore, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 610)
  - Memorial Album (Box 44, Folder 611)
    Includes photograph portrait; photographs of medals and certificates; photograph of Bowers and Gregg; photographs of consultancy with Ford Foundation in India (1952-1959); photograph of Bowers and Rajkumari Amrit Kaur; WHO First Regional Conference on medical Education and Training in the Western Pacific (1963); photograph with Lord Adrian and Lord Todd, Ciba Foundation Symposium (1974); photographs of visit to the Chinese Academy of Medical Sciences/Peking Union Medical College (1980); photograph of Bowers and Akiko Bowers, The Order of the Rising Sun (1982)
  - Nagasaki Photos, 1947 (Box 44, Folder 612-614)
    Taken by Shields Warren
  - Slides (Box 44, Folder 615-616)
  - "Medical Education in Japan: From Chinese Medicine to Western Medicine" by John Z. Bowers, 1965 (Box 45)
  - "Medical Education in Japan: From Chinese Medicine to Western Medicine" by John Z. Bowers, 1965 (Box 45)
  - Book Review by Professor Taizo Ogawa, 1966 (Box 45)
  - "Western Medical Pioneers in Feudal Japan" by John Z. Bowers (2 copies - paperback and hardcover), 1970 (Box 45)
  - "Western Medical Pioneers in Feudal Japan," "When The Twain Meet: The Rise of Western Medicine in Japan" by John Z. Bowers, 1970; 1980 (Box 45)
  - "Doctor on Desima: Five Years in Japan. Selected Chapters from JHR J.L.C. Pompe van Meerdervoort's 'Vijf Jaren in Japan'" translated and annotated by Elizabeth P. Wittermans and John Z. Bowers, 1970 (Box 45)
  - "Western Medicine in a Chinese Palace: Peking Union Medical College, 1917-1951" by John Z. Bowers, 1972 (Box 45)
  - NIH Publication No. 80-1496 [Possibly "An Introduction to American Medicine" by John Z. Bowers], 1980 (Box 45)
  - "An Introduction to American Medicine - 1975" by John Z. Bowers, 1977 (Box 45)
  - "When The Twain Meet: The Rise of Western Medicine in Japan" by John Z. Bowers, 1980 (Box 45)
  - "Medical Schools for the Modern World" edited by John Z. Bowers, 1970 (Box 45)
  - "Medical Schools for the Modern World" edited by John Z. Bowers, 1970 (Box 45)
  - "Migration of Medical Manpower" edited by John Z. Bowers and Lord Rosenheim, 1971 (Box 45)
  - "National Health Services: Their Impact on Medical Education and Their Role in Prevention" edited by John Z. Bowers and Elizabeth Purcell, 1973 (Box 45)
  - "Teaching the Basic Medical Sciences: Human Biology" edited by John Z. Bowers and Elizabeth F. Purcell, 1974 (Box 45)
  - "Schools of Public Health: Present and Future" edited by John Z. Bowers and Elizabeth F. Purcell, 1974 (Box 45)
  - "Medicine and Society in China" edited by John Z. Bowers and Elizabeth F. Purcell, 1974 (Box 46)
  - "Advances in American Medicine: Essays at the Bicentennial, Volume 1 and Volume 2" edited by John Z. Bowers and Elizabeth F. Purcell (2 volumes), 1976 (Box 46)
  - "The University and Medicine: The Past, The Present, and Tomorrow" edited by John Z. Bowers and Elizabeth F. Purcell, 1977 (Box 46)
  - "Opportunities for Philanthropy - 1976" edited by John Z. Bowers and Elizabeth F. Purcell, 1977 (Box 46)
  - "New Medical Schools at Home and Abroad" edited by John Z. Bowers and Elizabeth F. Purcell, 1978 (Box 46)
  - "The Impact of Health Services on Medical Education: A Global View" edited by John Z. Bowers and Elizabeth F. Purcell, 1978 (Box 46)
  - "Drug Assessment Criteria and Methods" edited by J.Z. Bowers and G.P. Velo, 1979 (Box 46)
  - "Aspects of the History of Medicine in Latin America" edited by John Z. Bowers and Elizabeth F. Purcell, 1979 (Box 46)
  - "The Current Status and Future of Academic Obstetrics" edited by John Z. Bowers and Elizabeth F. Purcell, 1980 (Box 46)
  - "Interaccion entre la Educacion y la Asistencia Sanitaria" edited by J.Z. Bowers, A. Gallego, F. Vilardell, A. Oriol Bosch, A. Gómez-Pan, 1981 (Box 46)
  - "Informe de los Expertos" edited by J.Z. Bowers, 1980 (Box 46)
  - "Letters from Meiji Japan: Correspondence of a German Surgeon's Wife, 1878-1881" by Charlotte T. Marshall in collaboration with John Z. Bowers, 1980 (Box 46)
  - "Letters from Meiji Japan: Correspondence of a German Surgeon's Wife, 1878-881" by John Z. Bowers, 1987 (Box 46)
  - "Academic Medicine: Present and Future" edited by John Z. Bowers and Edith E. King, 1983 (Box 46)
  - "Parasitology: A Global Perspective" edited by Kenneth S. Warren and John Z. Bowers, 1983 (Box 46)
  - "Science and Medicine in Twentieth-Century China: Research and Education" edited by John Z. Bowers, J. William Hess, and Nathan Sivin, 1988 (Box 46)
  - "Teaching the Biological and Medical Aspects of Reproduction to Medical Students", 1966 (Box 47)
  - "The Training and Responsibilities of the Midwife", 1967 (Box 47)
  - "Medical History and Medical Care: A Symposium of Perspectives", 1971 (Box 47)
  - "Thoughts from The Lake of Time: A Group of Essays in honor of The Villa Serbelloni and especially of John and Charlotte Marshall" edited by John Burchard, 1971 (Box 47)
  - "World Trends in Medical Education: Faculty, Students, and Curriculum" edited by Elizabeth Purcell, 1971 (Box 47)
  - "Case Histories of Ten New Medical Schools" edited by Vernon W. Lippard and Elizabeth Purcell, 1972 (Box 47)
  - "The Future Role of University-Based Metropolitan Medical Centers", 1972 (Box 47)
  - "Public Health in the People's Republic of China" edited by Myron E. Wegman, Tsung-yi Lin, and Elizabeth F. Purcell, 1973 (Box 47)
  - "Serve the People: Observations on Medicine in the People's Republic of China" by Victor W. Sidel and Ruth Sidel, 1973 (Box 47)
  - "A Half-Century of American Medical Education: 1920-1970" by Vernon W. Lippard, 1974 (Box 47)
  - "Proceedings of the Macy Conference on Teaching Tropical Medicine, New Orleans, Louisiana, 11-12 June 1973," Supplement to the American Journal of Tropical Medicine and Hygiene, 1974 (Box 47)
  - "Women in Medicine" by Carol Lopate, 1968 (Box 47)
  - "Health Care, Teaching and Research: Prospect and Retrospect; A Symposium Celebrating the Twenty-Fifth Anniversary of the Faculty of Medicine, The University of British Columbia, June 4-6, 1975" edited by William C. Gibson (Box 47)
  - "Puberty: Biologic and Psychosocial Components" edited by S.R. Berenberg, 1975 (Box 47)
  - "Physicians for the Future: Report of the Macy Commission", 1976 (Box 47)
  - "Recent Trends in Medical Education" edited by Elizabeth F. Purcell, 1976 (Box 47)
  - "Brain: Fetal and Infant: Current Research on Normal and Abnormal Development" edited by Samuel Berenberg, 1977 (Box 48)
  - "Medical Education and Medical Care: A Scottish-American Symposium", 1977 (Box 48)
  - "Minorities in Medicine: From Receptive Passivity to Positive Action, 1966-76" by Charles E. Odegaard, 1977 (Box 48)
  - "The Current Status and Future of Parasitology", 1981 (Box 48)
  - "The University Medical Center and the Metropolis" edited by Eli Ginzberg and Alive M. Yohalem, 1974 (Box 48)
  - "Campus Health Programs" edited by William Dalrymple and Elizabeth F. Purcell, 1976 (Box 48)
  - "Medicine Man: A Publication of the Class of 1951 College of Medicine, University of Utah: (Box 48)
  - "Medicine Man, Published by the Senior Class of the University of Utah College of Medicine", 1954 (Box 48)
  - "Condition Red: Destroyer Action in the South Pacific" by Commander Frederick J. Bell, U.S. Navy, 1943 (Box 48)
  - "Moon Music" by Faye Kellerman, 1998 (Box 48)
  - "The Current Era of the Faculty of Medicine, Columbia University, 1910-1958: (Box 48)
  - "The Dean: Willard C. Rappleye and the Evolution of American Medical Education" by Harry Atkins (Box 48)
  - "Genealogy of The Macy Family from 1635-1868" compiled by Silvanus J. Macy (Box 48)
  - "The Josiah Macy, Jr. Foundation, 1930-1955" (Box 48)
  - "Encounter with Disaster - A Medical Diary of Hiroshima, 1945" by Averill A. Liebow, 1965 (Box 48)
  - "We of Nagasaki: The Story of Survivors in an Atomic Wasteland" by Takashi Nagai, 1951 (Box 48)
  - "Explaining the Atom" by Selig Hecht, 1947 (Box 49)
  - "Document of A-Bombed Nagasaki" by Tatsuichiro Akizuki, 1977 (Box 49)
  - "Hiroshima Peace Reader" by Yoshiteru Kosakai, 1980 (Box 49)
  - "A Planet to Heal: Reflections and Forecasts" by Pedro Arrupe, S.J., 1975 (Box 49)
  - "Yo Vivi la Bomba Atomica y Memorias" by P. Pedro Arrupe, S.J., 1965 (Box 49)
  - "The Story of the Rockefeller Foundation" by Raymond B. Fosdick, 1952 (Box 49)
  - Siebold - Additional - Siebold and Dutch, Djakarta (Box 49)
    Removed from Box 3, Folder 71
  - AOA, Warren / Bowers, V-2837, U-matic (Box T1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact an archivist for further assistance.
  - "Leaders in American Medicine", 1980 February; U-matic; Mastered on 3/4" (Box T1)
    Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact an archivist for further information.